<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<dialog version="1.2" name="Narrator" auto-option-off="True">
  <options>
    <option text="Start" show="False" say="False">
      <script><![CDATA[PLAYER: Chicky's freestyle speech.
  Wait(80);
PLAYER: A gentleman enters a restaurant.
PLAYER: Red tables, red counter, red menu...
PLAYER: Delicious looking burgers, smell of hot oil and soft potatoes...
PLAYER: "Nothing has changed, it seems!"
PLAYER: Says the gentleman. Nothing changed, except for him.
PLAYER: When he left this place 25 years ago, he was young and tough.
PLAYER: Now he is as soft as those potatoes.
PLAYER: He tries to think other things.
PLAYER: He thinks his purpose, yes he has a purpose and he need to do,
PLAYER: Do what he couldn't 25 years ago.
PLAYER: He walks to counter and orders a side salad with ranch dressing,
PLAYER: Just like he did 25 years ago, in different circumstances.
PLAYER: He takes his tray and sits on one of the tables.
PLAYER: He'd love to taste the side salad, but that's not why he's here. 
PLAYER: He has no time to sit and eat.
PLAYER: He has something to do first.
PLAYER: He looks at voucher: 3323. Even password to restrooms didn't change.
PLAYER: "It still reads same word..."
PLAYER: He thinks. And slowly stands up.
PLAYER: He takes a deep breath befor entering restrooms.
PLAYER: And here he is again. He feels good when he realises something has changed.
PLAYER: Red tables, red counter, red menu...
PLAYER: But no red walls anymore. They are all gray now.
PLAYER: He looks to gray walls and remembers how white they were.
PLAYER: And he remembers how they got red.
PLAYER: He remembers what he did...
  FadeOut(10);
  Wait(20);
  FadeIn(10);
PLAYER: A young man entered the restaurant.
PLAYER: He looked like he has in hurry.
PLAYER: He passed red counter and red tables, didn't even looked at red menu.
PLAYER: He went directly to the restrooms but couldn't get whaat he wants.
PLAYER: "Damn door passwords! You can't even pee in peace..."
PLAYER: He grumbled.
PLAYER: He asked the password to the door to first costumer he saw.
PLAYER: The customer yelled "No!" 
PLAYER: "Those freeloaders!"
PLAYER: The young man squeezed his fist but said nothing.
PLAYER: He asked to another costumer, but couldn't get what he wanted again.
PLAYER: He decided to ask to employee instead of stupid costumers.
PLAYER: "I can't tell the password, you need to buy something to get it. Company pollicy."
PLAYER: He would be happy to buy something, but he just left his wallet at home.
PLAYER: He explained the situation but employee just ignored what he said.
PLAYER: "Company pollicy."
PLAYER: His hands started to shaking, but he didn't say anything.
PLAYER: Then se saw something. Saomething that could help him.
PLAYER: Someone left tray without dumping the garbage.
PLAYER: He quickly went to tray and checked voucher.
PLAYER: He left his anger behind, forgot about stupid costumers and employee,
PLAYER: He forgot about company pollicy and focused to password only.
PLAYER: He entered 3323 to keypad, and stepped into peace.
  FadeOut(10);
  Wait(20);
  FadeIn(10);
PLAYER: Well, he thought he stepped into peace at least.
PLAYER: Until he took a breath.
PLAYER: Until he tried to use toilet.
PLAYER: Until he saw the hell.
  Wait(40);
PLAYER: He got out of restroom. All the anger he left behind came back.
PLAYER: He was angry, more than that, he was furious.
PLAYER: He just wanted to find who did that.
PLAYER: He started to sniff people. Whoever did that, must left clues behind.
PLAYER: People got disturbed, but he didn't care. He used all his politeness that day.
PLAYER: And finally he thought he found the guilty.
PLAYER: "Did you do that?"
PLAYER: He asked. Guilty one just could say "Hah?"
PLAYER: "Your guilty just stinks out of you!"
PLAYER: He yelled. And then he hold guilty one's arm.
PLAYER: "Hey, leave me alone!" said the guilty one and pushed him.
PLAYER: That was the last drop. He started to chase the guilty one to restrooms.
PLAYER: But couldn't get him because he locked himself in the toilet.
PLAYER: He tried to push door but door was too strong.
PLAYER: Then he remembered a red fire extenguisher behind the counter.
PLAYER: He walked to counter but employee didn't look like let him to get the fire extenguisher.
PLAYER: He couldn't get in an snother fight. He did must find a way to get it.
PLAYER: He started to look around. And then he saw it. Saw the slution.
PLAYER: He needed to get rid of employee, and there was no ranch dressing left in fridge.
PLAYER: He ordered a side salad with ranch dressing.
PLAYER: Employee looked at him weird, he said he forgothis wallet  couple of minutes ago.
PLAYER: Also he almost got in a fight.
PLAYER: "Whatever..." crubled employee and went away to get ranch drressing.
PLAYER: After that, time went fast.
PLAYER: He took the f,re extenguisher.
PLAYER: He broke the restroom door.
PLAYER: Walls got red.
  FadeOut(10);
  Wait(20);
  FadeIn(10);
PLAYER: He shakes his head, put aways bad memories.
PLAYER: And walks to toilet.
PLAYER: Does what he couldn't do 25 years ago.
PLAYER: Pees in rest.

stop]]></script>
    </option>
  </options>
  <variables />
</dialog>